Guide to the Stanford News Service Audiovisual Recordings SC1125
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, News and Publication Service, audiovisual recordings
1936-2011
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. News and Publications Service
SC1125
63 Linear Feet and 17.4 gigabytes
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Audiotapes.; Stanford University -- History.; Stanford University -- Administration.; Videorecordings.; Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Stanford University. News and Publications Service
- Audiorecordings, circa 1971-2006; Series 1
  - Kennedy, Donald inauguration, 1980 Oct; 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Faculty Senate (CR), 1980 Oct 16; 2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Faculty Senate, Abel, El (Director of Tresidder), speech re: UNESCO-McBride Comm. (NR), 1980 Nov 13; 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Hufstader, Shirley (Sec. of Education) talk at Law School, 1980 Oct 31; 4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Donald. "Black presence at Stanford" (NR,CR p.1), 1980 Nov 20; 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - US-East Asia forum, Japan relations in Silicon Valley (John Lewis et al), 1980 Nov 13; 6; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - US-East Asia forum, Japan relations in Silicon Valley (John Lewis et al), 1980 Nov 13; 7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Royden, Halsey (CR), 1981 Jan 12; 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Freshman orientation (Keohane), 1980 Sept 26; 9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Panel on Poland (Wayne Vucinich), 10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Parents Day, 1980; 11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Shaw, Ed (CIT), 12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman-Clive Cooksen (London Times article on Higher Education), 1980 June 9; 13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Faculty Senate, 1980 Oct 2; 14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Boskin, Michael (economics) to GSB Alumni (text on file), 15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Cannon, Robert on Einstein Project (Observer, spring '80); Quate, Calvin on acostic microscope, 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Franklin, H. Bruce; Brown, Robert M, before occupation of placement center, 1972 May 9; 17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Franklin, H. Bruce, demonstration, 1972 Jan 24; 18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Harris, David, on draft, White Plaza (NR), 1980 Jan 24; 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Fagan, Richard on El Salvador and Nicaragua (NR), 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - KSZU Interview with Lyman, Richard W., 1980 Jan 25; 21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Committee on Investment Policy. R. Lyman on investment in South Africa, 22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Kidnapped students (Africa), 23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview by Mary Madison, Times Tribune, 1979 Fall; 24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Return from Anapurna (NR) in McCarthy file, 1978 Oct 27; 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview by Bill Tromblay, L.A. Times, 1976 Dec; 26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview re: protests, 1972 Jan 18; 27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Franklin, H. Bruce rally (?) press conference re: word from advisory committee, 1972 Jan 5; 28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Committee on Investment Policy, 1977 Nov 28; 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview, 1980 Jan 27; 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview on KZSU, 1974 Jan 8; 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview on KZSU, 1974 Apr 21; 32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Demonstration at Placement Center, 1972 Nov 12 (1973 Jan 18?); 33; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Dolly, John, arrest outside of GSB, 1972 Feb 5; 34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview on KZSU, 1976 Jan 26; 35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Lives for Radical Change statement re: recombanant DNA Cambridge, Mass. City council statement to Stanford Comm. on Bio. Hazards, 36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Rally for the "Stanford Indian," with Williams, Timm as main speaker; includes comments of native american students and Ziebell, Larry of Palo Alto, 37; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kennedy, Donald and Lyman, Richard W. following trustee meeting, following Kennedy's selection as president. Includes informal questions from reporters. (CR), spring 1980; 38; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Black Liberation Month Panel (NR 1-28-81; 2-6-81), 1981 Feb 5; 39; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Women in Management Panel, CR 2-4-81, p.13) Levin, Henry (Institute for Research in Ed'l finance & gov't) (CR 2-4-8l,p.14), 1981 Jan 31; 40; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Meyer, John (prof. of sociology; Institute for Research in Ed'l finance & gov't) re: education (CR, 2-4-81 p. 14), 1981 Feb 4; 41; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Atkin, Myron J. (Dean, education) re: education (CR 2-4-81, p.1), 1981 Feb 4; 42; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Beyers, Bob (Director, News Service) re: Hubert Humphrey incident, 1966, 1981 Feb; 43; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Terman, Frederick E., interview with Bob Beyers (Tape 1), 1973 Oct 31; 44; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Terman, Frederick E., interview with Bob Beyers (Tape 2), 1973 Oct 31; 45; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Falcon, Walter P. (Director and professor, FRI) talk to Stanford Library Associates, 1981 Feb 15; 46; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Los Angeles Conference: Paul Berg re: DNA (CR 3-11-81; 3-18-81), 1981 March; 47; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Los Angeles Conference: Ralph Smith re: microelectronics, 48; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Los Angeles Conference: Don Kennedy re: general outlook for the university, 49; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Friedman, Milton re: USSR and China (NR 3-9-81), 1981 Mar 9; 50; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Tannenbaum, Marc H., Baccalaureate speaker, 1980 Jun; 51; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview on KZSU (CR 5-21-80), 1980 May 21; 52; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Faculty Senate; primarily tributes to President Richard Lyman (CR 6-19-80), 1980 Jun 12; 53; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Protest against President Carter's visit to Portola Valley (CR 7-9-80,p.1), 1981 Jul 3; 54; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - McPherson, Rene C. (Dean, GSB) (NR, 7-16-80), 1980 Jul 16; 55; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kennedy, Donald, interview on KZSU (NR, 8-60-80), 1980 Aug 5; 56; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Clark, Ed (Libertarian candidate for president), at Stanford, 1980 Jul 4; 57; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Lyman, Richard W. interview by Cynthia Parsons, Christian Science Monitor, 1980 Spring; 58; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Class Day speakers, commencement, 1980 Jun; 59; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Anderson, John (Independent candidate for president), at Stanford (NR, 4-9-80), 1980 Apr 8; 60; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1979; 61; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Class Day, 1979; 62; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Dedication, Green Library, 1981 April; 63; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Committee on Research (TAPE ONE OF TWO), 1981 Mar 11; 64; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Committee on Research (TAPE TWO OF TWO), 1981 Mar 11; 65; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview with Lyman, Richard W. by San Jose Mercury, 1979 December; 66; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kennedy, Donald addressing alumni, San Francisco, con't Faculty Senate meeting, 1981 Apr 29-30; 67; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Anderson, John interview (at home, Stanford press conference) re: assassination attempt of Reagan, Alexander Haig, possible third party formation. Donald Lunde re: assassinations (poor recording), 1981 Apr 1; 68; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Glenn (30 minutes) and Freedman, Milton, 1980 Oct 29; 69; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Arthur Schawlow's press conference re: winning nobel prize, 1981; 70; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Teller, Edward- Drell, Sidney debate (Branner Hall) CR 1-20-82, 1982 Jan 14; 71; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1981; 72; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Class Day, 1981; 73; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - History Corner restoration dedication, 1980 Feb 8; 74; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Seeley Mudd Bldg. dedication, 1977 Mar 11; 75; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Green Library groundbreaking, 1977 Feb 8; 76; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Investment Policy: Panel on South Africa, Cubberley Aud., 1977 Mar 7; 77-78; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Investment Policy: Forum, Cubberley Aud., 1977 Apr 6; 79-80; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Progressive Student Conference; I.F. Stone re: Reagan, 1982 Mar 6; 81; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Panel on research (with C. Djerassi, D. Kennedy, Wm Smith) Universities, industries and graduate education, 1982 Apr 26; 82; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Diaconis, Persi (CR 7-14-82), 1982 Jul 9; 83; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Kennedy, Hastorf at Stanford volunteer Program, 1982 Sept 13; 84; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Class day, Cecil Green talk, Green Library, 1982 Jun 14; 85; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Baccalaureate sermon, 1982 June; 86; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Faculty Senate, 1982 Sept 28; 87; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Parents Day, 1982 Sept 23; 88; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Faculty Senate, 1982 Dec 2; 89; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Faculty Senate CIT, 1983 Jan 6; 90; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Huff, Robt. Financial Aid, 1982 Dec 9; 91; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Pauling, Linus on peace, 1983 Mar 15; 92; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - A. Re: Eliz visit, Jeanna K.; GLAS Conference w/Univ. Attorneys on Scholarship Offer, 1983 Feb 23; 93; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Boskin; Proctor, 1983 Jan 12-13; 94; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - McCarthy, Grads in common; Knight, Andrew CEPR, 1983; 95; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Fuller, Karmen III retirement, 1983; 96; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Rehab R&D outer, director Prof. Larry Leifer CR 2-9-83, 1983 Feb 9; 97; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Barchas, Samuel C., 1981?; 98; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Comm on research hearing, 1982 Spring?; 99; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Forsythe Bldg. ground breaking, 1989 Jan 14; 100; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - CIS Bldg ground breaking, Rich. De Laver CR, 1983?; 101; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Tobin. endowed prof. lecture n.d. (CR), 102; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - 25th Anniv. Of Soc. @ SU, 1982?; 103; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Simon, Herb. SU Press book, 1982 Feb 11; 104; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Weinbager, Casper Demoshahai, 1982 Mar 14; 105; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Roth, Barnie NoCal Sci writers conf. (CR), 1982 Aug 11; 106; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Hofstedler, Shirley. Talk to law students., 1982 Mar; 107; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Jahns, Richard. LA conference; Esslin, Kennedy, 1983 Mar 7; 108; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Zimbardo, Phillip G., student stress panel, 1982 Apr; 109; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Majano, Salvadorian refugee talks re El S. (no CR), 1982 May 5; 110; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - C Econ. Res. Panel. Baker, H; Arrow, K; M. Friedman, 1983 Mar 14; 111; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - KZSU/Kennedy, 1982 May 26; 112; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Kennedy, David to frosh, 1982 Sep 24; 113; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Massy on USW w/students Academic Council, 1982 Oct 8; 114; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Baratz, Michael (union leader) USW after strikes, 1982 Oct 8; 115; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Japan Panel Dan Okamoto re: Japanese challenge CR, 1982 Dec 2; 116; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Mosher, Steven press conf. & Barnett w/reporters, 117; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Mosher & Barnett, choir anthro, 1983 Feb 24; 118; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Mosher, 1983 Feb 25; 120; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Mosher 60 Minutes, 1983 June 12; 121; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Barnett 60 Minutes, 1983 Mar 1; 122; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Mosher, Today Show; Faculty Senate, 1983 Mar 7; 123; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - LA conference - Pascal, B; Bunzel, 1983 Mar 7; 124; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson, Eric, 1982 Apr 1; 125; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Profs. In performance, 1983 Apr; 126; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Lewis, John, Campus Report, 1983 Apr 27; 127; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - SSRL Demonstration; Wood, Panofsky--Arms Control, 1983 Ap-May; 128; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Panofsky, Wolfgang K.H. - Wood debate; Shultz demonstration, 1983 May 4; 129; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Levin, Hauk 1FG interview; Kirst, Michael, 1983 May; 130; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Mnookin. Alumni conference; Shulman, Lees, 1983 May 14; 131; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Arms Protest, 1983 June 1; 132; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Class Day (Kennedy?), 1983 June 11; 133; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Carter, Jimmy. Visit., 1983 Jul 15; 134; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Student Senate debate Req. lib; Faculty Senate, 1983 Oct 25-27; 135; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Kennedy, Donald. KZSU, 1983 Nov; 136; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Smith, Charles. C for Lang Inst. ND, Undated; 137; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Reaganville. Cecil Williams/Kirst., 1982 May 8?; 138; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Galbraith. Conf? Entrepreneur Conf. Howard Head CR, 1982 Apr 2; 139; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Jobs, Steve. Entrepreneur Conf. #2, 1982 Apr 3; 140; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - McKim, Robert; Vesper; Prowie. Entrepreneur #3, 1982 Apr 3; 141; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Faculty Senate, 1982 Feb 4; 142; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Faculty Senate, 1982 Mar 4; 143; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Faculty Senate, 1982 Apr 1; 144; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1981 Apr 29; 145; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate Library RLG, 1982 May 13; 146; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate Undergrad. Ed., 1982 May 27; 147; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1982 Oct 14; 148; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate CR Wessels, 1983 Apr 24; 149; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate CR Wessels, 1983 May 12; 150; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate; Hoover Debate, 1983 May; 151; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1983 Sept 29; 152; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1983 Oct 13; 153; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1983 Nov; 154; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1983 Dec 1; 155; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Pajaro Dunes #7 & #8, Undated; 156; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Chinese delegations, CIS building, 1985 Jul 28; 157; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Fall Convocation, Gibbs, Lyons, Thayer, et al, 1985 Sept 22; 158; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Parents Day/ J. Rosse, 1982; 159; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Allamandola, Louis, 2001 Mar 13; 160; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Cialdini, Robert, 2001 Feb 28; 161; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Carson, Clayborne, 2000 Jan 8; 162; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Freccero, John, 2001 Feb 12; 163; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Gilmore, Dan, Apr 18; 164; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Kim, Stuart, 2001 Jan 5; 165; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Perry, John, 2001 Mar 8; 166; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Rakove, Jack, 2001 Nov 7; 167; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Sullivan, Evelin, 2000 Nov 6; 168; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Sapolsky, Robert, 2001 Mar 14; 169; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Music Search for Stanford Museum Opening, 1998 Dec 1; 170-171; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Fasting Protest/Gordon Earle; KPFA Evening News, KPFA FM San Francisco 6-7PM, 2003 Jun 4; 03-0604-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Lewis, John; All Things Considered, National Public Radion, 5-6PM, 2994 Jan 10; 04-0110-1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Google, Morning Edition, National Public Radio, 6-7AM; Morning Edition, National Public Radion, 6-7AM, 2004 Apr 13, 15; 04-0413-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Sea of Cortez, Morning Edition, National Public Radio, 7-8AM, 2004 May 20-21; 04-0520-1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Exxon Mobile, Morning Drive Time, KGO-AM (ABC), San Francisco, 6-7AM, 2002 Nov 20; 172; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Exxon Mobile, Business for Breakfast, KKZN-AM, Denver, 9-10AM, 2002 Nov 21; 173; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Exxon Mobile, Business News at Noon, KRLD-AM (CBS), Dallas, 12PM, 2002 Nov 20; 174; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Tommy Lee Woon, 5/1/2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ramon Saldivar, 3/6/2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Hersh - Kresge Auditorium 7:30PM, 10/19/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Life Sciences Symposium Bldg. 320/105 Tape 1 Side 1, 4/15/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Life Sciences Symposium Bldg. 320/105 Tape 2 Side 2, 4/15/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - European Roundtable VII Tape 2, 10/28/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Gavin Wright, Winter 2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - CSP Bldg. 320/105 Tape 2/2, 2/4/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - CISAC Drell Lecture Father J. Bryan Mehir, 12/6/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - European Roundtable VII Tape 1, 10/28/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ronald Barrett Family Caregiving in an Aging World at Cubberley Auditorium, 3/4/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - CSP Bldg. 320/105 Tape 1/2, 2/4/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - European Roundtable VI Tape 1 Side 1, 4/8/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - European Roundtable VI Tape 2 Side 2, 4/8/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Seymar Hersh at Kresge Auditorium, 10/19/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Memorial Auditorium Roundtable Forum Tape 1, 10/17/2003; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Memorial Auditorium Roundtable Forum Tape 2, 10/17/2003; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ellen Waxman, 2/27/2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Robin MAmlet, 5/15/2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Luis Fraga, 10/23/2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - A. Bradley, 1/28/1998; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - President of Ireland, 9/20/1999; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - 3 Books Talk Frosh Memorial Auditorium Side B, 9/21/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Tudor Rose, 12/3/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Jim Thompson Positive Coaching Alliance, Radio interview, 1/1/2004; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - A. Master, 10/11/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - C.W. Francis Everitt Side A Only 2/2, 5/18/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Tudor Rose, 12/3/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - C.W. Francis Everitt Side A Only 1/2, 5/18/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Aging and the Perception of Time, 3/4/2006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Class of 1950 Class Panel (55th Reunion), 10/21/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - Class of '65 Panel, 10/21/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - From Despair to Hope? The Reconstruction of New Orleans and its effect on US Poverty, 10/22/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - 50 Class Panel, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - 55 Class Panel 50th Reunion, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - 55 Class Panel 50th Reunion Tape 2, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - #53830 McCaw Hall, 10/21/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - Stanford Mixed Company 20th Anniversary Reunion Concert, 10/22/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - Stanford Reunion Homecoming, 10/21/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
  - Stanford Roundtable Forum Spill (Tape 2), 10/21/2005; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8)
- Videorecordings, 1936-2011; Series 2
  - Rose Bowl, 1936, Stanford vs. Southern Methodist University, 1936 Jan 1; 36-0101-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Length: 00:29:00
    Black and White/ Silent, highlights of the Rose Bowl Game from 1936. Tape includes a shot list/ work order for the tape. The footage is from the Tournament of Roses. It was transferred from U-Matic on April 14, 1988. The notes state there are focus problems. The game is notable for being the first Rose Bowl to sell out all seats.
  - Stanford Campus Views, 1993 May 20; 93-0520; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    STANFORD CAMPUS VIEWS 1993: Seminar Cubberley Kresge Econ Bio Labs Gilbert
  - GPS Press Conference (13), 10/18/1994; 94-1018-7; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    [This is likely related to the GPS landing system for planes through the Integrity Beacon. Tape is labeled as 13.]
  - Stanford GPS, Graphics & Animation, Dub, 10/18/1994; 94-1018-9; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    It contains animation about the test using the Global Positioning Satellite System (GPS) to land planes.
  - GPS integrity Beacon Landing system, 11/00/1994; 94-1100-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    Length: 00:10:00
    Animation Graphic; Exterior Landing; Cockpit Camera; Antennas; Circuit Boards; Ground Researchers; Sound Bites; About the launch of the Integrity Beacon. It uses GPS to help with traffic control and the landing of planes. Stanford's Integrity Beacon Landing System uses ground-based pseudo-satellite transmitters known as Integrity Beacons to resolve carrier phase ambiguities on final approach, giving IBLS both high integrity and centimeter-level accuracy.
  - Gravity Probe B, #1, Bardas, Original, 12/05/1994; 94-1205-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    Gravity Probe B was designed to measure two key predictions of Einstein's general theory of relativity by monitoring the orientations of ultra-sensitive gyroscopes relative to a distant guide star. Doron Bardas description of on-going work, Interview.
  - Gravity Probe B, #2, Original, 12/05/1994; 94-1205-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    Gravity Probe B was designed to measure two key predictions of Einstein's general theory of relativity by monitoring the orientations of ultra-sensitive gyroscopes relative to a distant guide star.
  - Gravity Probe B, #3, Original, 12/06/1994 - 12/07/1994; 94-1206-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
  - Gravity Probe B, #6, Original, 12/09/1994; 94-1209-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    Gravity Probe B was designed to measure two key predictions of Einstein's general theory of relativity by monitoring the orientations of ultra-sensitive gyroscopes relative to a distant guide star. Doron Bardas Interview, outside window.
  - Pac 10 institutional spot, 12/21/1994; 94-1221-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    Company reel
  - Stanford Promo 1995, Gail Mahood, Master, 95-0000-4; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    Stanford promotional video from 1995 It contains a geology class with Gail Mahood, geology professor and various campus shots.
  - Interviews with Nordson, Schmidt, Birrell, Dahan, 04/20/1995; 95-0420-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    INTERVIEWS WITH BILL NADAR NORDSON 1995 GLEN SCHMIDT DIANA BIRRELL ELY DAHAN B-roll
  - Lynn Utter, President GSB, Alumni Association Interview, John Browne, 04/20/1995; 95-0420-2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)
    LYNNE UTTER President S.U. GSB Alumni Association interview John Browne, British Petroleum
  - Incoming Student Pizza Party, 04/21/1995; 95-0421-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 1)